[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Thailand, pink is associated with what day of the week?", "correct_answer": "Tuesday", "incorrect_answers": ["Wednesday", "Saturday", "Friday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robin Williams starred in Mrs. Doubtfire. Another great actor, Dustin Hoffman starred in Tootsie. Both characters pretended to be this.", "correct_answer": "Women", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead", "Insane", "Bed-ridden and sick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the South African Airways Flight 295 crash on 28 November 1987?", "correct_answer": "Indian ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["Madagascar", "Mediterranean sea", "Morocco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1997 film is this quote from: Evolution has a way of keeping things alive.", "correct_answer": "Mimic", "incorrect_answers": ["Bats", "From Dusk Til Dawn", "Vampires"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the reaction called when an acid and a base are mixed together?", "correct_answer": "neutralization", "incorrect_answers": ["single replacement", "double replacement", "synthesis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was Roman Maronie deported in the movie Johnny Dangerously?", "correct_answer": "Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Mexico", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This star, the second brightest star in the constellation Orion, is a red supergiant.", "correct_answer": "Betelgeuse", "incorrect_answers": ["Spica", "Pollux", "Sirius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where and when does the opening scene of The Last Crusade take place?", "correct_answer": "Utah, 1912", "incorrect_answers": ["New Mexico, 1910", "New Mexico, 1913", "Utah, 1911"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jane Leeves, who is famous for her roles on Frasier and Seinfeld, first worked for which comedian?", "correct_answer": "Benny Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Hendra", "Jerry Lewis", "Flip Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much of an effective range do skunks odor glands have?", "correct_answer": "15 feet", "incorrect_answers": ["10 feet", "8 feet", "20 feet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of soviet, as in Soviet Union?", "correct_answer": "Council", "incorrect_answers": ["Socialistic", "Communist", "Republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the metric system, what unit is used to measure temperature?", "correct_answer": "degrees Kelvin", "incorrect_answers": ["degrees Fahrenheit", "degrees Centigrade(Celsius)", "degrees Rankine"]}]